让你的程序简洁的运行在模拟器上，
The simplicity of hitting run and having your app appear on an emulator,
规避冗余。哦，别忘了，Android是完全的软件叠层架构。
hides a lot of complexity. Remember that Android is a full software stack.
Adspace 是 Linux 内核，
Adspace is a Linux Kernel,
它可以处理硬件性能和面板管理能力低的任务。
which handles low level tasks like hardware fibers and panel management.
更重要的是，一些核心C和C++库，像 Libsc、SQLite 和 Android运行库。
On top of that, are some core C and C plus plus libraries like Libsc and
这包括简单的Android库和Android虚拟机，
SQLite and the Android Runtime. That includes cool Android libraries and
Dalvik或者近期出的ART。
the Android virtual machines, Dalvik or more recently ART. Your apps run
你的程序运行需要应用程序在虚拟机上使用类、服务、框架进行实例化。
within its own instance of the VM using the classes and services provided here
最重要的是，你的程序位于应用层，
in the application framework. On top of that, sits the application layer,
这里也是设备上其他程序安装的地方。
which includes your app and every other app that's installed on the device. So,
所以，当你在Android Studio点击运行你的程序时，
when you hit Run in Android Studio, the first thing that happens is your code
首先得将你的代码编译成虚拟机可以运行的字节代码。
gets compiled into byte code that can be run in the Android Virtual Machine.
而这个代码会被再次放到到机器上。
That then gets installed onto the device. In Android Studio,
在Android Studio上，我们会使用gradle构建一个工具包，来管理依赖关系，
this is done using gradle, a build tool kit that manages dependencies and
并允许自定义逻辑。
allows you to define custom build logic.
你可以选择自己建立一个gradle，然后构建IDE。
You can manually start a gradle build in the IDE by selecting make project.
你也可以构建菜单和选项来实现，
You can also do this by going to the build menu and selecting make project from
或者你可以使用gradle观察到任何的日志和报错，
there, or you can use the gradle console to observe any logs or
或者打开gradle的任务窗口，查看还在生存周期中的任务。
build errors, or open the gradle tasks window to see any available tasks.
双击任何一个都会执行。这将会在命令行界面工作。
Double clicking on any of them will execute it. This will work from
一旦你进到项目文件夹的根目录下，
the command line too. Once you've navigated to the root of your project folder,
你就可以运行gradle查看所有运行的任务。
you can run gradlew tasks to see all the tasks that you can run. You can learn
你可以通过查看讲师笔记学习到更多关于gradle的知识。
more about gradle by checking out the links in the instructor notes. For now,
现在我们首先是一个Android project，然后建立gradle，
note that we start with the project, which gradle then builds and
在gradle里有转换过的字节代码，外部资源像图片、字符串，
then packages the byte code along with the external resources such as images,
和应用程序包里的UIXML。这构成了APK,
strings, and uixml into an application package. This is called an APK, and
实际上这一个特殊格式的压缩文件。当你准备好APK时,
it's a specially formatted zip file. Once you've got your APK ready to go,
下一步就是，签名还有推送到设备上使用ADB
it's signed and then pushed to the device using the Android Debug Bridge or
如果回到终端，我们可以看见ADB可以让你在任何设备上与程序交互、调试，
ADB. If we return to the terminal, you can see that ADB lets you interact and
不管是虚拟机还是物理机。比如像上传、下载文件，
debug apps on any device, physical or virtual. Things like pushing and
输出日志，
pulling files, viewing logcat output, or
甚至运行一个远程的shell。一旦 APK 中发现 android's GDO 已安装 ADB，
even running a remote shell. So once Android's GDO has ADB installed the APK,
它将ADB再次发送远程shell命令，
it uses ADB again to launch the app by sending a stock command via the remote
通过识别您的package和class name来启动应用程序。
shell, by identifying the package and class name of your main activity.